A Guide to the Tredegar Iron Works Records, 1801-1957
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Correspondence, Inletters, 1872-1957, Extent: 231.45 cu. ft. (656 boxes). (Box 205-860)
  - Subseries 1: General, 1872-1957, Extent: 194.95 cu. ft. (557 boxes). (Box 205-761)
    - 1892, Crerar, Adams & Co. (January-April) (Box-folder 303:3)
    - 1892, Crerar, Adams & Co. (May- July) (Box-folder 303:4)
    - 1892, Crerar, Adams & Co. (August-October) (Box-folder 303:5)
    - 1892 Ea (Box-folder 303:6)
    - 1892, Ec-Ew (Box-folder 304:1)
    - 1892, Foote (May-June) (Box-folder 304:2)
    - 1892, Foote (July-August) (Box-folder 304:3)
    - 1892, Foote (September-October) (Box-folder 304:4)
    - 1892, Ga (Box-folder 304:5)
    - 1892, Ge-Gi (Box-folder 304:6)
    - 1892, Gl-Gu (Box-folder 305:1)
    - 1892, Hac-Hal (Box-folder 305:2)
    - 1892, Ham-Har (Box-folder 305:3)
    - 1892, Has-Hay (Box-folder 305:4)
    - 1892, Hea-Hey (Box-folder 305:5)
    - 1892, Hi-Hob (Box-folder 305:6)
    - 1892, Hoffman (Box-folder 305:7)
    - 1892, Hog-Hy (Box-folder 305:8)
    - 1892, Mic-Mit (Box-folder 306:1)
    - 1892, Mo-My (Box-folder 306:2)
    - 1892, Na (May-September) (Box-folder 306:3)
    - 1892, Ne (May-September) (Box-folder 306:4)
    - 1892, Ni-No (May-September) (Box-folder 306:5)
    - 1892, Na (October-December) (Box-folder 306:6)
    - 1892, Ne (October-December) (Box-folder 306:7)
    - 1892, Ni-No (October-December) (Box-folder 306:8)
    - 1892, O (May-September) (Box-folder 306:9)
    - 1892, O (October-December) (Box-folder 307:1)
    - 1892, P (May-September) (Box-folder 307:2)
    - 1892, P (October-December) (Box-folder 307:3)
    - 1892, Ra-Re (January-July) (Box-folder 307:4)
    - 1892, Richards - Richland (January-July) (Box-folder 307:5)
    - 1892, Richmond Cedar - R,F, & P (January-July) (Box-folder 307:6)
    - 1892, Richmond & Danville Railroad Co. (January-May) (Box-folder 307:7)
    - 1892, Richmond Locomotive - Richmond Railway Co. (January-July) (Box-folder 307:8)
    - 1892, Richmond Standard Co. - Rich Patch Iron Co. (January-July) (Box-folder 307:9)
    - 1892, Rie-Ru (January-July) (Box-folder 307:10)
    - 1892, Q-Rh (August-December) (Box-folder 308:1)
    - 1892, Richards - Richmond Chamber of Commerce (August-December) (Box-folder 308:2)
    - 1892, Richmond & Danville Railroad Co. (August-December) (Box-folder 308:3)
    - 1892, R,F, & P - Richmond Locomotive Co. (August-December) (Box-folder 308:4)
    - 1892, Richmond & Manchester RailwayCo. - Rich Patch Iron Co. (August-December) (Box-folder 308:5)
    - 1892, Rie-Ru (August-December) (Box-folder 308:6)
    - 1892, Sa (Box-folder 308:7)
    - 1892, Sc (Box-folder 308:8)
    - 1892, Se-Sh (Box-folder 308:9)
    - 1892, Si-Sl (Box-folder 308:10)
    - 1892, Sm-Sn (Box-folder 309:1)
    - 1892, So (Box-folder 309:2)
    - 1892, Sp-Sw (Box-folder 309:3)
    - 1893, Ab-Al (Box-folder 309:4)
    - 1893, Am-Au (Box-folder 309:5)
    - 1893, Ba (Box-folder 309:6)
    - 1893, Bec-Ben (Box-folder 309:7)
    - 1893, Ber-Bl (Box-folder 310:1)
    - 1893, Bo-Bro (Box-folder 310:2)
    - 1893, Bru-Bu (Box-folder 310:3)
    - 1893, Ca (Box-folder 310:4)
    - 1893, Ce-Ch (Box-folder 310:5)
    - 1893, Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad Co. (January-April) (Box-folder 310:6)
    - 1893, Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad Co. (May-August) (Box-folder 310:7)
    - 1893, Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad Co. (September-December) (Box-folder 310:8)
    - 1893, Ci-Cl (Box-folder 311:1)
    - 1893, Co-Cu (Box-folder 311:2)
    - 1893, Crerar, Adams & Co. (January- February) (Box-folder 311:3)
    - 1893, Crerar, Adams & Co. (March-May) (Box-folder 311:4)
    - 1893, Crerar, Adams & Co. (June-July) (Box-folder 311:5)
    - 1893, Crerar, Adams & Co. (August-December) (Box-folder 311:6)
    - 1893, D (Box-folder 312:1)
    - 1893, Ea (Box-folder 312:2)
    - 1893, Ed-Ev (Box-folder 312:3)
    - 1893, Fa-Fi (Box-folder 312:4)
    - 1893, Fl (Box-folder 312:5)
    - 1893, Fo-Fra (Box-folder 312:6)
    - 1892, Foote (November-December) (Box-folder 312:7)
    - 1893, Foote (January) (Box-folder 313:1)
    - 1893, Foote (February-March) (Box-folder 313:2)
    - 1893, Foote (April-May) (Box-folder 313:3)
    - 1893, Fre-Fu (Box-folder 313:4)
    - 1893, Ga-Ge (Box-folder 313:5)
    - 1893, Gi-Gu (Box-folder 313:6)
    - 1893, Hac-Har (Box-folder 313:7)
    - 1893, Has-Hey (Box-folder 314:1)
    - 1893, I-Je (Box-folder 314:2)
    - 1893, Jo (Box-folder 314:3)
    - 1893, Ka-Kei (Box-folder 314:4)
    - 1893, Kel-Kn (Box-folder 314:5)
    - 1893, McClung - McNamee (Box-folder 314:6)
    - 1893, Ma (Box-folder 314:7)
    - 1893, Ma (Box-folder 315:1)
    - 1893, Me (Box-folder 315:2)
    - 1893, Na (January-May) (Box-folder 315:3)
    - 1893, Ne (January-May) (Box-folder 315:4)
    - 1893, Ni-No (January-May) (Box-folder 315:5)
    - 1893, Na (October-December) (Box-folder 315:6)
    - 1893, Ne (October-December) (Box-folder 315:7)
    - 1893, Ni-No (October-December) (Box-folder 315:8)
    - 1893, O (January-May) (Box-folder 315:9)
    - 1893, O (October-December) (Box-folder 316:1)
    - 1893, P (January-May) (Box-folder 316:2)
    - 1893, P (October-December) (Box-folder 316:3)
    - 1893, Ra-Re (January-September) (Box-folder 316:4)
    - 1893, Richardson - R,F, & P (January-September) (Box-folder 316:5)
    - 1893, Richmond Locomotive Co. - Richmond & Manchester Railway Co. (January-September) (Box-folder 316:6)
    - 1893, Richmond Standard Spike & Iron Co. (January-September) (Box-folder 316:7)
    - 1893, Ril-Ro (January-September) (Box-folder 316:8)
    - 1893, Q-Re (October-December) (Box-folder 316:9)
    - 1893, Re-Ro (October-December) (Box-folder 317:1)
    - 1893, Richardson - Rich Patch Iron Co. (October-December) (Box-folder 317:2)
    - 1893, Sm (Box-folder 317:3)
    - 1893, Sn-So (Box-folder 317:4)
    - 1893, Sp-Ste (Box-folder 317:5)
    - 1893, Sto-Sw (Box-folder 317:6)
    - 1894, Ca (January-July) (Box-folder 317:7)
    - 1894, Ce-Ci (January-July) (Box-folder 318:1)
    - 1894, Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad Co. (January-August) (Box-folder 318:2)
    - 1894, Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad Co. (September-December) (Box-folder 318:3)
    - 1894, Cl-Cy (January-July) (Box-folder 318:4)
    - 1894, Ca (August-November) (Box-folder 318:5)
    - 1894, Ce-Ch (August-November) (Box-folder 318:6)
    - 1894, Cl-Cu (August-November) (Box-folder 319:1)
    - 1894, Crerar, Adams & Co. (January-May) (Box-folder 319:2)
    - 1894, Crerar, Adams & Co. (June-September) (Box-folder 319:3)
    - 1894 October-1895 January, Crerar, Adams & Co. (Box-folder 319:4)
    - 1894 July, Da (January-1895) (Box-folder 319:5)
    - 1894, De-Do (January-1895 July) (Box-folder 320:1)
    - 1894, Dr-Du (January-1895 July) (Box-folder 320:2)
    - 1894, Ea (January-1895 July) (Box-folder 320:3)
    - 1894, Eb-El (January-1895 July) (Box-folder 320:4)
    - 1894, Em-Ex (January-1895 July) (Box-folder 320:5)
    - 1894, Foote (January-March) (Box-folder 320:6)
    - 1894, Foote (April-June) (Box-folder 320:7)
    - 1894, Foote (July-September) (Box-folder 321:1)
    - 1894, Ga (Box-folder 321:2)
    - 1894, Ge-Gi (Box-folder 321:3)
    - 1894, Gl-Gu (Box-folder 321:4)
    - 1894, Hab-Han (January-1896 July) (Box-folder 321:5)
    - 1894, Har-Hay (January-1896 July) (Box-folder 321:6)
    - 1894, He (January-1896 July) (Box-folder 321:7)
    - 1894, La-Le (January-1895 March) (Box-folder 322:1)
    - 1894, Li-Loe (January-1895 March) (Box-folder 322:2)
    - 1894, Lor-Ly (January-1895 March) (Box-folder 322:3)
    - 1894, Mi (January-September) (Box-folder 322:4)
    - 1894, Mo-Mu (January-September) (Box-folder 322:5)
    - 1894, Mi-My (October-1895 April) (Box-folder 322:6)
    - 1894, O (Box-folder 322:7)
    - 1894, P (Box-folder 322:8)
    - 1894, Q-Ra (Box-folder 323:1)
    - 1894, Richmond & Danville Railroad Co. (January-September) (Box-folder 323:2)
    - 1894, Re-Ric (Box-folder 323:3)
    - 1894, Rid-Ru (Box-folder 323:4)
    - 1894, Sa (Box-folder 323:5)
    - 1894, Sc (Box-folder 323:6)
    - 1894, Se-Sl (Box-folder 324:1)
    - 1894, Southern Railway Co. (January-September) (Box-folder 324:2)
    - 1894, Southern Railway Co. (October-December) (Box-folder 324:3)
    - 1894, Wab-Wat (January-1895 March) (Box-folder 324:4)
    - 1894, Way (January-1895 March) (Box-folder 324:5)
    - 1894, We (January-1895 March) (Box-folder 324:6)
    - 1894, Wh (January-1895 March) (Box-folder 324:7)
    - 1894, Wad-Wan (August-1896 February) (Box-folder 325:1)
    - 1894, War-Wel (August-1896 February) (Box-folder 325:2)
    - 1894, Wes-Wh (August-1896 February) (Box-folder 325:3)
    - 1895, Ad-Al (January-June) (Box-folder 325:4)
    - 1895, Am-As (January-June) (Box-folder 325:5)
    - 1895, At-Av (January-June) (Box-folder 325:6)
    - 1895, Ab-Al (July-October) (Box-folder 325:7)
    - 1895, Am-As (July-October) (Box-folder 326:1)
    - 1895, At-Av (July-October) (Box-folder 326:2)
    - 1895, Ab-Al (October-1896 March) (Box-folder 326:3)
    - 1895, Am-Ax (October-1896 March) (Box-folder 326:4)
    - 1895, At-Av (October-1896 March) (Box-folder 326:5)
    - 1895, Bab-Bal (August-1896 March) (Box-folder 326:6)
    - 1895, Ban-Bel (March-1896 August) (Box-folder 327:1)
    - 1895, Ben-Bl (March-1896 August) (Box-folder 327:2)
    - 1895, Bo-Bri (March-1896 August) (Box-folder 327:3)
    - 1895, Bro-Bry (March-1896 August) (Box-folder 327:4)
    - 1895, Bu-By (August-1896 August) (Box-folder 327:5)
    - 1895, Ca (Box-folder 327:6)
    - 1895, Ce-Ch (Box-folder 327:7)
    - 1895, Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co. (January-July) (Box-folder 328:1)
    - 1895, Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co. (July-September) (Box-folder 328:2)
    - 1895, Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co. (October-December) (Box-folder 328:3)
    - 1895, Cl-Cu (Box-folder 328:4)
    - 1895, Fa (July-1896 June) (Box-folder 328:5)
    - 1895, Fe-Fl (July-1896 June) (Box-folder 328:6)
    - 1895, Fo-Fr (July-1896 June) (Box-folder 329:1)
    - 1895, Ga (Box-folder 329:2)
    - 1895, Ge (Box-folder 329:3)
    - 1895, Gi-Gu (Box-folder 329:4)
    - 1895, H (March-1898 December) (Box-folder 329:5)
    - 1895, Hoc-Hof (August-1896 June) (Box-folder 329:6)
    - 1895, Hol-Hy (August-1896 June) (Box-folder 330:1)
    - 1895, La-Lev (April-1896 March) (Box-folder 330:2)
    - 1895, Lewis-Loe (April-1896 March) (Box-folder 330:3)
    - 1895, Loh-Ly (April-1896 March) (Box-folder 330:4)
    - 1895, Mc-Man (September-1896 July) (Box-folder 330:5)
    - 1895, Mar-May (September-1896 July) (Box-folder 330:6)
    - 1895, Me (September-1896 July) (Box-folder 330:7)
    - 1895, Na (February-June) (Box-folder 331:1)
    - 1895, Ne-Ni (February-June) (Box-folder 331:2)
    - 1895, No-Nu (February-June) (Box-folder 331:3)
    - 1895, Na-Ne (July-October) (Box-folder 331:4)
    - 1895, Ni-No (July-October) (Box-folder 331:5)
    - 1895, O (February-June) (Box-folder 331:6)
    - 1895, O (July-October) (Box-folder 331:7)
    - 1895, P (July-October) (Box-folder 331:8)
    - 1895, Sa-Sc (February-1896 July) (Box-folder 332:1)
    - 1895, Se-Sh (February-1896 July) (Box-folder 332:2)
    - 1895, Si-Sl (February-1896 July) (Box-folder 332:3)
    - 1895, Sm-Sn (January-June) (Box-folder 332:4)
    - 1895, So (January-June) (Box-folder 332:5)
    - 1895, Southern Railway Co. (January-June) (Box-folder 332:6)
    - 1895, Sp-Su (January-June) (Box-folder 332:7)
    - 1895, Sm (July-November) (Box-folder 333:1)
    - 1895, So (July-November) (Box-folder 333:2)
    - 1895, Sp-Sy (July-November) (Box-folder 333:3)
    - 1895, Sm (December-1896 July) (Box-folder 333:4)
    - 1895, So (December-1896 July) (Box-folder 333:5)
    - 1895, Sp-Sy (December-1896 July) (Box-folder 333:6)
    - 1896, Ab-Al (Box-folder 333:7)
    - 1896, Am-Ar (Box-folder 334:1)
    - 1896, At-Av (Box-folder 334:2)
    - 1896, Baa-Bak (Box-folder 334:3)
    - 1896, Bal-Bar (Box-folder 334:4)
    - 1896, Be (Box-folder 334:5)
    - 1896 Bi-Bl (Box-folder 334:6)
    - 1896, Ca (January-June) (Box-folder 334:7)
    - 1896, Ce-Cha (January-June) (Box-folder 335:1)
    - 1896, Che-Cle (January-June) (Box-folder 335:2)
    - 1896, Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad Co. (January-June) (Box-folder 335:3)
    - 1896, Co-Cu (January-June) (Box-folder 335:4)
    - 1896, Crerar, Adams & Co. (January-June) (Box-folder 335:5)
    - 1896, Ca (July-December) (Box-folder 335:6)
    - 1896, Ce-Cha (July-December) (Box-folder 335:7)
    - 1896, Che-Cu (July-December) (Box-folder 335:8)
    - 1896, Ea-Em (Box-folder 336:1)
    - 1896, En (Box-folder 336:2)
    - 1896, Fa-Fli (Box-folder 336:3)
    - 1896, Flo-Fu (Box-folder 336:4)
    - 1896, Ga-Ge (Box-folder 336:5)
    - 1896, Gi-Gu (Box-folder 336:6)
    - 1896, Ha-He (July-1897 January) (Box-folder 336:7)
    - 1896, Ha (September-1898 April) (Box-folder 337:1)
    - 1896, He (September-1898 April) (Box-folder 337:2)
    - 1896, Hi-Hof (November-1897 September) (Box-folder 337:3)
    - 1896, Hol-I (November-1897 September) (Box-folder 337:4)
    - 1896, J (Box-folder 337:5)
    - 1896, K (Box-folder 337:6)
    - 1896, La-Le (Box-folder 337:7)
    - 1896, Li-Loe (Box-folder 338:1)
    - 1896, Lov-Ly (Box-folder 338:2)
    - 1896, Mi-My (January-May) (Box-folder 338:3)
    - 1896, Mi-My (June-December) (Box-folder 338:4)
    - 1896, Na-Ne (Box-folder 338:5)
    - 1896, Ni-Nu (Box-folder 338:6)
    - 1896, O (Box-folder 338:7)
    - 1896, Pa-Pe (Box-folder 339:1)
    - 1896, Pi-Pu (Box-folder 339:2)
    - 1896, Q-Ri (Box-folder 339:3)
    - 1896, Ro-Ry (Box-folder 339:4)
    - 1896, Sa-Sl (Box-folder 339:5)
    - 1896, Smi-So (Box-folder 339:6)
    - 1896, Southern Railway Co. (January-February) (Box-folder 340:1)
    - 1896, Southern Railway Co. (March-April) (Box-folder 340:2)
    - 1896, Southern Railway Co. (May-June) (Box-folder 340:3)
    - 1896, Southern Railway Co. (July-August) (Box-folder 340:4)
    - 1896, Southern Railway Co. (September-October) (Box-folder 340:5)
    - 1896, Southern Railway Co. (November-December) (Box-folder 340:6)
    - 1896, Sp-Sy (Box-folder 341:1)
    - 1896, T-V (Box-folder 341:2)
    - 1896, Wi (Box-folder 341:3)
    - 1896, Wo-Z (Box-folder 341:4)
    - 1897, Ab-Al (January-June) (Box-folder 341:5)
    - 1897, Am-As (January-June) (Box-folder 341:6)
    - 1897, At-Au (January-June) (Box-folder 341:7)
    - 1897, Ab-Al (December-1898 March) (Box-folder 342:1)
    - 1897, Am-An (December-1898 March) (Box-folder 342:2)
    - 1897, Atlantic Coast Line (January-March) (Box-folder 342:3)
    - 1897, Atlantic Coast Line (April-September) (Box-folder 342:4)
    - 1897, Atlantic Coast Line (October-December) (Box-folder 342:5)
    - 1897, Atlantic & Danville Railway Co. (Box-folder 342:6)
    - 1897, Bai-Bak (Box-folder 342:7)
    - 1897, Bal (Box-folder 343:1)
    - 1897, Ban-Bar (Box-folder 343:2)
    - 1897, Bat-Bel (Box-folder 343:3)
    - 1897, Ben-Bl (Box-folder 343:4)
    - 1897, Bo-Bro (Box-folder 343:5)
    - 1897, Bru-Bu (Box-folder 343:6)
    - 1897, Ca (January-April) (Box-folder 343:7)
    - 1897, Ce-Ci (January-April) (Box-folder 344:1)
    - 1897, Cl-Cu (January-April) (Box-folder 344:2)
    - 1897, Ca (May-August) (Box-folder 344:3)
    - 1897 May-August, Ce-Cl (Box-folder 344:4)
    - 1897, Ca (September-November) (Box-folder 344:5)
    - 1897, Ce-Ci (September-November) (Box-folder 344:6)
    - 1897, Cl-Cr (September-November) (Box-folder 345:1)
    - 1897, Da-De (Box-folder 345:2)
    - 1897, Di-Du (Box-folder 345:3)
    - 1897, Fa-Fi (January-1898 March) (Box-folder 345:4)
    - 1897, Fl-Fo (January-1898 March) (Box-folder 345:5)
    - 1897, Fr-Fu (January-1898 March) (Box-folder 345:6)
    - 1897, Ga-Ge (January-August) (Box-folder 346:1)
    - 1897, Gi-Gu (January-August) (Box-folder 346:2)
    - 1897, Ga-Ge (October-1898 March) (Box-folder 346:3)
    - 1897, Gi-Gu (October-1898 March) (Box-folder 346:4)
    - 1897, H (December-1898 April) (Box-folder 346:5)
    - 1897, I-Jo (January-September) (Box-folder 346:6)
    - 1897, Ju-Kr (January-September) (Box-folder 346:7)
    - 1897, I-J (September-1898 September) (Box-folder 347:1)
    - 1897, K (September-1898 September) (Box-folder 347:2)
    - 1897, La-Ll (Box-folder 347:3)
    - 1898, Lo-Ly (Box-folder 347:4)
    - 1897, Mc-May (Box-folder 347:5)
    - 1897, Me (Box-folder 347:6)
    - 1897, Mi-Mor (Box-folder 348:1)
    - 1897, Mot-My (Box-folder 348:2)
    - 1897, Na-Ni (May-August) (Box-folder 348:3)
    - 1897, No (May-August) (Box-folder 348:4)
    - 1897, Na-Ne (September-November) (Box-folder 348:5)
    - 1897, Ni-No (September-November) (Box-folder 348:6)
    - 1897, Na-Ni (December-1898 June) (Box-folder 348:7)
    - 1897, No (December-1898 June) (Box-folder 348:8)
    - 1897, O (May-August) (Box-folder 349:1)
    - 1897, O (September-November) (Box-folder 349:2)
    - 1897, O (December-1898 June) (Box-folder 349:3)
    - 1897, P (May-August) (Box-folder 349:4)
    - 1897, P (September-November) (Box-folder 349:5)
    - 1897, Pa (November-1898 March) (Box-folder 349:6)
    - 1897, Pe-Pr (November-1898 March) (Box-folder 350:1)
    - 1897, Ra-Ri (January-September) (Box-folder 350:2)
    - 1897, Ro-Ru (January-September) (Box-folder 350:3)
    - 1897, Ra-Ric (October-1898 March) (Box-folder 350:4)
    - 1897, Rid-Ru (October-1898 March) (Box-folder 350:5)
    - 1897, Sa-Sc (Box-folder 350:6)
    - 1897, Se-Sh (Box-folder 351:1)
    - 1897, Si-Sl (Box-folder 351:2)
    - 1897, Sm-Sn (Box-folder 351:3)
    - 1897, So (Box-folder 351:4)
    - 1897, Sp-Sy (Box-folder 351:5)
    - 1897, Sm-Sn (January-August) (Box-folder 351:6)
    - 1897, So (January-August) (Box-folder 351:7)
    - 1897, Sp-Sy (January-August) (Box-folder 351:8)
    - 1897, Sm (January-1899 March) (Box-folder 352:1)
    - 1897, Sn-So (January-1899 March) (Box-folder 352:2)
    - 1897, T (Box-folder 352:3)
    - 1897, U-V (Box-folder 352:4)
    - 1897, Wa-Wei (Box-folder 352:5)
    - 1897, Wel-Whi (Box-folder 352:6)
    - 1898, Ab-Al (April-August) (Box-folder 353:1)
    - 1898, Am-As (April-August) (Box-folder 353:2)
    - 1898, At (April-August) (Box-folder 353:3)
    - 1898, Ab-Ale (September-December) (Box-folder 353:4)
    - 1898, All-An (September-December) (Box-folder 353:5)
    - 1898, Ar-Atlantic Coast Line (September-December) (Box-folder 353:6)
    - 1898, Atlantic & Danville Railway Co. - Augusta Railway Co. (September-December) (Box-folder 353:7)
    - 1898, Ba (January-March) (Box-folder 354:1)
    - 1898, Be-Bl (January-March) (Box-folder 354:2)
    - 1898, Ba (April-August) (Box-folder 354:3)
    - 1898, Be-Bl (April-August) (Box-folder 354:4)
    - 1898, Bai-Ban (September-1899 February) (Box-folder 354:5)
    - 1898, Bar-Bay (September-1899 February) (Box-folder 354:6)
    - 1898, Bea-Bel (September-1899 February) (Box-folder 354:7)
    - 1898, Bel (September-1899 February) (Box-folder 355:1)
    - 1898, Bem-Bl (September-1899 February) (Box-folder 355:2)
    - 1898, Ca (August-December) (Box-folder 355:3)
    - 1898, Ce-Cha (August-December) (Box-folder 355:4)
    - 1898, Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co. (January-March) (Box-folder 355:5)
    - 1898, Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co. (April-September) (Box-folder 355:6)
    - 1898, Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co. (September-December) (Box-folder 355:7)
    - 1898, Crerar, Adams & Co. (April-August) (see oversize) (Box-folder 356:1)
    - 1898, Crerar, Adams & Co. (September-December) (Box-folder 356:2)
    - 1898, Da-De (Box-folder 356:3)
    - 1898, Di-Du (Box-folder 356:4)
    - 1898, Ea-En (January-August) (Box-folder 356:5)
    - 1898, Er-Ey (January-August) (Box-folder 356:6)
    - 1898, Ea-Em (October-1899 August) (Box-folder 356:7)
    - 1898, En (October-1899 August) (Box-folder 357:1)
    - 1898, Er-Ev (October-1899 August) (Box-folder 357:2)
    - 1898, Ga (October-1899 August) (Box-folder 357:3)
    - 1898, Ge (October-1899 August) (Box-folder 357:4)
    - 1898, Gi-Gl (October-1899 August) (Box-folder 357:5)
    - 1898, Go-Gu (October-1899 August) (Box-folder 357:6)
    - 1898, Ha (April-1899 August) (Box-folder 357:7)
    - 1898, He (April-1899 August) (Box-folder 358:1)
    - 1898, I-Je (June-1899 June) (Box-folder 358:2)
    - 1898, Joh-Jon (June-1899 June) (Box-folder 358:3)
    - 1898, Jos-Joy (June-1899 June) (Box-folder 358:4)
    - 1898, Ka-Ke (April-1899 April) (Box-folder 358:5)
    - 1898, Ki-Kr (April-1899 April) (Box-folder 358:6)
    - 1898, La-Le (April-1899 April) (see oversize) (Box-folder 359:1)
    - 1898, Li-Ll (April-1899 April) (Box-folder 359:2)
    - 1898, Loe-Lov (April-1899 April) (Box-folder 359:3)
    - 1898, Low-Ly (April-1899 April) (Box-folder 359:4)
    - 1898, McA-McL (April-September) (Box-folder 359:5)
    - 1898, Ma (April-September) (Box-folder 359:6)
    - 1898, Me (April-September) (Box-folder 360:1)
    - 1898, McC (October-1899 June) (Box-folder 360:2)
    - 1898, McD-McM (October-1899 June) (Box-folder 360:3)
    - 1898,Mac-Mat (October-1899 June) (Box-folder 360:4)
    - 1898, May-Me (October-1899 June) (Box-folder 360:5)
    - 1898, Mi (October-1899 June) (Box-folder 360:6)
    - 1898, Mob-Mor (October-1899 June) (Box-folder 360:7)
    - 1898, Mot-My (October-1899 June) (Box-folder 361:1)
    - 1898, Na-Ne (April-August) (Box-folder 361:2)
    - 1898, Ni-No (April-August) (Box-folder 361:3)
    - 1898, O (April-August) (Box-folder 361:4)
    - 1898, Pa-Pe (April-August) (Box-folder 361:5)
    - 1898, Pi-Pu (April-August) (Box-folder 361:6)
    - 1898, Ra-Rh (May-1899 June) (Box-folder 361:7)
    - 1898, Richards - Richmond Locomotive (May-1899 June) (Box-folder 361:8)
    - 1898, Richmond & Manchester - Riverton Mills Co. (May-1899 June) (Box-folder 361:9)
    - 1898, Ro-Ry (May-1899 June) (Box-folder 362:1)
    - 1898, Sa (Box-folder 362:2)
    - 1898, Sc-Se (Box-folder 362:3)
    - 1898, Sh (Box-folder 362:4)
    - 1898, Si-Sl (Box-folder 362:5)
    - 1898, Sm-So (Box-folder 362:6)
    - 1898, Southern Railroad Co. (April-May) (Box-folder 363:1)
    - 1898, Southern Railroad Co. (June-July) (Box-folder 363:2)
    - 1898, Southern Railroad Co. (August-September) (Box-folder 363:3)
    - 1898, Southern Railroad Co. (October) (Box-folder 363:4)
    - 1898, Southern Railroad Co. (November-December) (Box-folder 363:5)
    - 1898, St-Su (Box-folder 364:1)
    - 1898, T (April-August) (Box-folder 364:2)
    - 1898, U (April-August) (Box-folder 364:3)
    - 1898, V (April-August) (Box-folder 364:4)
    - 1898, U (September-1899 May) (Box-folder 364:5)
    - 1898, V (September-1899 May) (Box-folder 364:6)
    - 1898, Web-Weh (Box-folder 364:7)
    - 1898 Wei-Wh (Box-folder 364:8)
    - 1898, Wil-Win (Box-folder 365:1)
    - 1898, Wis-Z (Box-folder 365:2)
    - 1899, Ab-Al (Box-folder 365:3)
    - 1899, Am-As (Box-folder 365:4)
    - 1899, Atlantic Coast Line (Box-folder 365:5)
    - 1899, At-Au (Box-folder 365:6)
    - 1899, Ca (Box-folder 365:7)
    - 1899, Ce (Box-folder 366:1)
    - 1899, Ch-Cl (Box-folder 366:2)
    - 1899, Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co. (January-April) (Box-folder 366:3)
    - 1899, Co-Cu (Box-folder 366:4)
    - 1899, E (Box-folder 366:5)
    - 1899, Fa-Fl (Box-folder 366:6)
    - 1899, Fo-Fu (Box-folder 366:7)
    - 1899, Ha (Box-folder 367:1)
    - 1899, He (Box-folder 367:2)
    - 1899, Hi (Box-folder 367:3)
    - 1899, Ho-Hu (Box-folder 367:4)
    - 1899, R.C. Hoffman & Co. (Box-folder 367:5)
    - 1899, I-J (Box-folder 367:6)
    - 1899, K (Box-folder 367:7)
    - 1899, La-Le (Box-folder 368:1)
    - 1899, Li-Lo (Box-folder 368:2)
    - 1899, Mi-Moo (Box-folder 368:3)
    - 1899, Mor-My (Box-folder 368:4)
    - 1899, N (Box-folder 368:5)
    - 1899, O (Box-folder 368:6)
    - 1899, Pa-Pi (January-May) (Box-folder 368:7)
    - 1899, Pl-Pu (January-May) (Box-folder 369:1)
    - 1899, Pa (June-September) (Box-folder 369:2)
    - 1899, Pe-Pi (June-September) (Box-folder 369:3)
    - 1899, Pl-Pu (June-September) (Box-folder 369:4)
    - 1899, Q-Rh (Box-folder 369:5)
    - 1899, Ri (Box-folder 369:6)